quiz = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "What is the first name of Iron Man?",
        "answer" : "Tony"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "Who is called the god of lightning in Avengers?",
        "answer" : "Thor"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "Who carries a shield of American flag theme in Avengers?",
        "answer" : "Captain America"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "Which avenger is green in color?",
        "answer" : "Hulk"
    },
    5 : {
        "question" : "Which avenger can change it's size?",
        "answer" : "AntMan"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "Which Avenger is red in color and has mind stone?",
        "answer" : "Vision"
    },
    7: {
        "question" : "Where did Killmonger grow up?",
        "answer" : "Oakland, California"
    },
    8: {
        "question" : "___ Parker is Peter Parker’s aunt’s name?",
        "answer" : "May"
    },
    9: {
        "question" : "Which Infinity Stone does Vision have in his head?",
        "answer" : "Mind Stone"
    },
    10: {
        "question" : "What is Tony Stark’s daughter’s name?",
        "answer" : "Morgan"
    },
    11: {
        "question" : "What planet is Thanos from?",
        "answer" : "Titan"
    },
    12: {
        "question" : "What AI replaces JARVIS?",
        "answer" : "FRIDAY"
    },
    13: {
        "question" : "What chemical do the Avengers use to travel in time in Avengers: Endgame?",
        "answer" : "Pym particles"
    },
    14: {
        "question" : "What kind of doctor was Dr. Stephen Strange?",
        "answer" : "Neurosurgeon"
    },
    15: {
        "question" : " Which eye does Thor lose?",
        "answer" : "Right"
    },
}
